The Corona Pandemic is a worldwide business.
This is something that affects a lot of people, finances and numbers.
If one is to understand the development-
-It is often best included with graphs and statistics.
But that does not mean that all graphs show the truth.
The difficult thing is to understand the statistics right, like Edwin's absurd hopes.
But then see me.
What claims are wrong?
You make it sound like I drank 20 cups only on Sunday.
But you have summarized all the cups for my household all over the weekend.
Then you present that figure that it applies to be a day.
This is how the figures about how many people have died in Corona have been reported.
Then the figures will be higher, although in fact, one assumes for days.
A bit like you did here, your cheeky.
-The curve is often much more even.
-But not everyone knows.
We called Peter Håkansson-
-Whith has written the book "Statistics in the news".
His sister -in -law in Croatia had heard about Sweden on the news.
Large increase in the number of dead.
We must explain that this is not true.
We have this backlog over the weekend-
-And then there will be new peaks when the backlog comes.
In addition, Edwin, your statistics are extensive.
You have brought water, decaffeinated tea and soft drinks.
So here it is in Sweden.
We include more and more in our statistics and our data.
Other countries do not include those who die in old age homes.
Therefore, we get bigger but also more accurate figures.
We are told here already-
-This in some other countries you become aware of much later.
Okay, maybe it was a little cheating with the graph.
But still, 15 cups you have been drinking.
15!
How sick is it, Åsa?
There you are wrong.
You count copper per household.
It makes it sound like I've been drinking everyone alone.
I have three people in my household and everyone has been drinking coffee this weekend.
Small countries' figures will always look worse than large countries.
But the picture then?
I have a photo proof where you sit with a lot of cups.
It's a classic trick.
The picture is taken from a tricky angle.
This is the same as the picture the police in Stockholm posted.
It looks packed on the street-
-and there some taverns on the street were later closed-
-To they had had too poor infection protection mode.
But there is still a point here.
How far do you think it's-
-Between the left corner of the picture and the lightboard you see there?
-Scare 30-40 m. -90 m it really is.